<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fundamentals of Computers and Pc-software on BCA Notes</title>
    <link>https://examplesite.com/fundamentals-of-computers-and-pc-software/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fundamentals of Computers and Pc-software on BCA Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Made with ❤ by Vishal Dongre</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://examplesite.com/fundamentals-of-computers-and-pc-software/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 1</title>
      <link>https://examplesite.com/fundamentals-of-computers-and-pc-software/unit-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://examplesite.com/fundamentals-of-computers-and-pc-software/unit-1/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Computers: History of development of Computer The history of the computer dates back to several years. There are four prominent generations of computers. Each generation has witnessed several technological advances which change the functionality of the computers. This results in more compact, powerful, robust systems which are less expensive. The computer as we know it today had its beginning with a 19th century English mathematics professor name Charles Babbage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 2</title>
      <link>https://examplesite.com/fundamentals-of-computers-and-pc-software/unit-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://examplesite.com/fundamentals-of-computers-and-pc-software/unit-2/</guid>
      <description>Windows: A window is a separate viewing area on a computer display screen in a system that allows multiple viewing areas as part of a graphical user interface ( GUI ). Windows are managed by a windows manager as part of a windowing system . A window can usually be resized by the user.
features of windows — desktop The desktop is the main screen area that you see after you turn on your computer and log on to Windows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 3</title>
      <link>https://examplesite.com/fundamentals-of-computers-and-pc-software/unit-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://examplesite.com/fundamentals-of-computers-and-pc-software/unit-3/</guid>
      <description> Introduction To Spreadsheet (MS-Excel): Definition And Advantages of Electronic Worksheet Working On Spreadsheets: Cell Referencing Range &amp;amp; Related Operations Setting, Saving And Retrieving Worksheet File Inserting, Deleting, Copying And Moving of Data Cells Inserting And Deleting Rows &amp;amp; Columns Copying, inserting, Renaming the sheet of workbook General Short-cut commands Entering text and numeric data Entering date and time different functions formatting text and numeric data Functions and Other Features: Classification and Usage of Various Built-In-Functions In Worksheet Passwords Protecting A Worksheet Printing of the worksheet page margin setting and adding header and footer Transferring Data to and From Non Worksheet Files Database Handling Creating, Naming &amp;amp; Executing Macros Creating graphs </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 4</title>
      <link>https://examplesite.com/fundamentals-of-computers-and-pc-software/unit-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://examplesite.com/fundamentals-of-computers-and-pc-software/unit-4/</guid>
      <description> PC Maintenance and Troubleshooting: Opening the PC and identification Study of different blocks Assembling and disassembling  Basic Device Configuration and Installation- Printers Microphone Monitor Mother Board Sound Card Video Card  tips on Trouble Shooting  Introduction to Computer Hardware Components of Mother-boards &amp;amp; its types Ports Slots Connectors add on cards Power supply units cabinet types  Storage devices: Primary storage medium Secondary storage medium  Introduction to servers and network security Types of servers: Files servers Email Servers Proxy servers etc  Basics of Internet and Intranet: Types of Internet connections: Dialup Broadband Leased Line Wi-Fi Wi-Max 2G 3G 4G WWW, E-mails Search Engines Social Networking Cloud application Audio-video Conferencing Voice over Internet Protocol (VOIP) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 5</title>
      <link>https://examplesite.com/fundamentals-of-computers-and-pc-software/unit-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://examplesite.com/fundamentals-of-computers-and-pc-software/unit-5/</guid>
      <description> Overview of System Analysis and Design Business System Concepts System Development Life Cycle Preliminary Investigation Feasibility Study System Analysis System Design and Testing Implementation &amp;amp; Evaluation  Overview of MIS: Introduction Role of IT MIS - characteristics and application areas Business and Technology trends - specialization, management by methodology decentralization internationalization etc  Characteristics of a good Business Unit Data and Information Difference between data and information Introduction to data Processing Fields Records Files Types of files: Master files Transaction file  Introduction to ERP  Introduction to SCM </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://examplesite.com/fundamentals-of-computers-and-pc-software/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://examplesite.com/fundamentals-of-computers-and-pc-software/resources/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
