<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>BCA Notes</title>
    <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/</link>
    <description>Recent content on BCA Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Made with ❤ by Vishal Dongre</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/about/</guid>
      <description> Vishal Dongre  Tanmay Tank  Rupenjay Choudhary  Shivam Goswamy  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 1</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/accounting-and-financial-management/unit-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/accounting-and-financial-management/unit-1/</guid>
      <description> Introduction Financial Accounting-definition and Scope Objectives Of Financial Accounting Accounting V/S Book Keeping Terms Used In Accounting Users Of Accounting Information Limitations Of Financial Accounting </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 1</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/cloud-computing-concepts/unit-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/cloud-computing-concepts/unit-1/</guid>
      <description> Introduction: Historical development Vision of Cloud Computing  Characteristics of Cloud Computing as per NIST  Cloud Computing reference model  Cloud computing environments  Cloud services equirements  Cloud and dynamic infrastructure  Cloud Adoption and rudiments  Overview of cloud applications: EGC Analysis in the cloud Protein structure predication Gene Expression Data Analysis Satellite Image Processing CRM /and ERP Social Networking.\ </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 1</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-graphics-with-multimedia/unit-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-graphics-with-multimedia/unit-1/</guid>
      <description>Coming soon&amp;hellip; Be patient 🙂 Good things takes time. 😉 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 1</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-neworks/unit-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-neworks/unit-1/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Computer Network - A system of interconnected computers that enable the computers to communicate with each other and share their resources, data and applications.
 Components  Node - A computer or device which is capable of sending and receving data. Message - Video, Audio, Document, any type of infromation, etc Sender - Computer/device which sends the message. Reciver - Computer/device which receives the message. Medium - through which message moves from a node to another node coaxial cable, fiber optics, radio waves, etc Protocol - TCP, UDP, FTP, SMTP etc   Goals  Resource Sharing Improved Performance High Reliability Flexible access Cost reduction (Save money ) Scalability Inter-process communication Access remote information etc   Applications (Uses)  eCommerce  B2C - Business to Consumer B2B - Business to Business C2C - Consumer to Consumer G2C - Government to Consumer P2P - Peer to Peer   File sharing Streming videos or audios Video calls etc   Network Criteria  Performance - measured by transit time and response time  Transit time - time for a message to travel from one device to another Response time - time between an inquiry and a response   Reliability - measured in terms of  Frequency of failures Recovery from failures   Security - protecting data from unauthorized access   Computer Network Models Responsible for establishing a connection among the sender and receiver and also for trasmitting the data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 1</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-oriented-numerical-methods/unit-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-oriented-numerical-methods/unit-1/</guid>
      <description> NUMERICAL COMPUTATIONS  Computer Arithmetic Floating Point Number Operations, Normalization and their consequences.  Iterative Methods : Bisection Methods, False Position Methods, Newton Raphson Method, Secant Method, Graffes Root Squaring Method, Convergence of Solution </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 1</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-system-architecture/unit-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-system-architecture/unit-1/</guid>
      <description> Data Representation- Data types, Number Systems: Binary Number system, Octal Number system Hexa–Decimal Number system.  Fixed-Point Representation: 1s &amp;amp; 2s complement, Binary fixed-point representation.  Arithmetic operation on binary numbers, overflow &amp;amp; underflow. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 1</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/cyber-security/unit-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/cyber-security/unit-1/</guid>
      <description>Basics of Communication Systems  Transmission Media Transmission media is a communication channel that carries the information from the sender to the receiver.The main functionality of the transmission media is to carry the information in the form of bits through LAN(Local Area Network). It is a physical path between transmitter and receiver in data communication.The transmission media is available in the lowest layer of the OSI reference model.Transmission media is of two types are wired media and wireless media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 1</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/data-structures-using-c&#43;&#43;/unit-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/data-structures-using-c&#43;&#43;/unit-1/</guid>
      <description> Introduction  Oops Languages  Characteristics Of Oop‘s Languages  Application Of Oop‘s  Oop‘s Paradigm Concepts: Object Class Data Abstraction Data Encapsulation Inheritance And Polymorphism Static And Dynamic Binding Message Passing  Benefits Of Oop‘s  Disadvantage Of Oop‘s </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 1</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/database-management-system-rdbms/unit-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/database-management-system-rdbms/unit-1/</guid>
      <description>Purpose of database system  views of data  data models: relation network hierarchical instances schemas  data dictionary  types of database languages:- DDL DML DCL TCL  structure of DBMS  advantages and disadvantages of DBMS  3-level architecture proposal:- external levels conceptual levels internal levels.  Database System architecture  level of abstraction  Database users and DBA,  Classification of Database Management Systems  Components of database system  Traditional File Systems vs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 1</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/fundamentals-of-computers-and-pc-software/unit-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/fundamentals-of-computers-and-pc-software/unit-1/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Computers: History of development of Computer The history of the computer dates back to several years. There are four prominent generations of computers. Each generation has witnessed several technological advances which change the functionality of the computers. This results in more compact, powerful, robust systems which are less expensive. The computer as we know it today had its beginning with a 19th century English mathematics professor name Charles Babbage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 1</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/internet-web-technology/unit-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/internet-web-technology/unit-1/</guid>
      <description> Introduction to Internet: Internet Growth of Internet Owners of the Internet Anatomy of Internet ARPANET and Internet history of the World Wide Web basic Internet Terminology Net etiquette  Internet Applications - Commerce on the Internet Governance on the Internet  Impact of Internet on Society - Crime on/through the Internet  Internet Technology and Protocol: Packet switching technology Internet Protocol TCP/IP Router  Internet Addressing Scheme: Machine Addressing (IP address) E-mail Addresses Resources Addresses </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 1</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/management-information-system/unit-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/management-information-system/unit-1/</guid>
      <description> Management &amp;amp; Organizational Support Systems For Digital Firm: Definition of MIS; Systems approach to MIS: Report writing s/w MIS and Human factor, Considerations concept of organizational information sub-system MIS &amp;amp; problem solving Case Studies </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 1</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/object-oriented-programming-concepts-using-java/unit-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/object-oriented-programming-concepts-using-java/unit-1/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Java  Java is a programming language and a platform. Java is a high level, robust, object-oriented and secure programming language.
Java was developed by Sun Microsystems (which is now the subsidiary of Oracle) in the year 1995. James Gosling is known as the father of Java. Before Java, its name was Oak. Since Oak was already a registered company, so James Gosling and his team changed the Oak name to Java.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 1</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/operating-system-with-unix-linux/unit-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/operating-system-with-unix-linux/unit-1/</guid>
      <description> Introduction to Operating Systems Operating system services multiprogramming time sharing system storage structures system calls multiprocessor system  Basic concepts of CPU scheduling Scheduling criteria Scheduling algorithms algorithm evaluation, multiple processor scheduling real time scheduling  I/0 devices organization I/0 buffering </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 1</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/programming-and-problem-solving-through-c/unit-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/programming-and-problem-solving-through-c/unit-1/</guid>
      <description> Programming Introduction Programming languages Classification of programming language: Structured programming concepts modular programming top-down programming approach Types of Programming languages Low level language Machine language (1GL) Assembly language (2GL) High level language Procedural-Oriented language (3GL) Problem-Oriented language (4GL) Natural language (5GL)  Problem solving using computer: coding, compilation debugging and testing documentation implementation and maintenance  Problem-Solving Techniques: Steps for Problem-Solving Design of Algorithms Definition, Features of Algorithm Flowcharts Basic Symbols used in Flowchart Design  C Language History of C salient Features of C Structure of a C Program a Simple C Program Compiling a C Program, Link and Run the C Program </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 1</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/software-engineering/unit-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/software-engineering/unit-1/</guid>
      <description> Introduction to Software Engineering : Software Engineering Software Process Generic process model Prescriptive process model specialized unified process- Agile development- Agile Process Extreme Programming Other agile Process models Software engineering Knowledge- core Principles- Principles that guide each framework Activity </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 1</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/web-programming/unit-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/web-programming/unit-1/</guid>
      <description> Web Technology: Introduction to WWW Web browsers Web servers HTTP URL  HTML: Introduction Objective HTML Command Tags: Text List Table Creation of links Inserting graphics, Forms  Cascading style sheets (CSS): Introduction to CSS Creating style sheets Types of CSS </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 1 Set Theory</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/discrete-mathematics-and-algebra/unit-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/discrete-mathematics-and-algebra/unit-1/</guid>
      <description> Sets Definition of Sets Venn Diagrams complements Cartesian products power sets counting principle, cardinality and countability (Countable and Uncountable sets) proofs of some general identities on sets, pigeonhole principle.  Relation: Definition types of relation composition of relations domain and range of a relation pictorial representation of relation properties of relation partial ordering relation. Function: Definition and types of function composition of functions recursively defined functions. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 2</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/accounting-and-financial-management/unit-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/accounting-and-financial-management/unit-2/</guid>
      <description> Conceptual Frame work: Accounting Concepts Principles And Conventions Accounting Standards Concept Objectives Benefits Brief Review Of Accounting Standards In India Accounting Policies, Accounting As A Measurement Discipline Valuation Principles Accounting Estimates </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 2</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/cloud-computing-concepts/unit-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/cloud-computing-concepts/unit-2/</guid>
      <description> Cloud Computing Architecture: Cloud Reference Model Types of Clouds, Cloud Interoperability &amp;amp; Standards Scalability and fault tolerance  Cloud Solutions: Cloud Ecosystem Cloud Business Process Management Cloud Service Management  Cloud Offerings: Cloud Analytics Testing Under Control Virtual Desktop Infrastructure. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 2</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-graphics-with-multimedia/unit-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-graphics-with-multimedia/unit-2/</guid>
      <description>Coming soon&amp;hellip; Be patient 🙂 Good things takes time. 😉 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 2</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-neworks/unit-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-neworks/unit-2/</guid>
      <description>Data Link Layer:  Design Issues, Framing, Error detection: Parity Check, LRC, VRC, Check Sum Cyclic Redundancy Check (CRC)  Correction Technique: Hamming code Flow Control:  Elementary Data Link Protocols: An Unrestricted Simplex Protocol, Simplex Stop-and-Wait Protocol, Sliding Window Protocols: One-Bit Sliding Window Protocol, Go Back N and Selective Repeat Data link layer in the Internet: SLIP and PPP</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 2</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-oriented-numerical-methods/unit-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-oriented-numerical-methods/unit-2/</guid>
      <description> Simultaneous Liner Equation : Solution of Simultaneous Liner Equation – Gauss Elimination Method, Gauss – Seidal Method, Gauss – Jordan Elimination Method, Triangularization Method &amp;amp; Pivoting Condensation, III Conditioned Equation &amp;amp; Refinement of solution  Curve Fitting : Curve Fitting Method, Least Curve Fitting, Non Linear Curve Fitting. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 2</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-system-architecture/unit-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-system-architecture/unit-2/</guid>
      <description> Digital Logic Ctrcuits: Logic Gates, And,Or,Not,Gate&amp;amp; Their Truth Tables, Nor, Nand &amp;amp; Xor Gates  Boolean Algebra Demorgan‘s Theorem.  Map Stmplocation: Minimization Techniques, K-Map  Sum Of Product &amp;amp; Product Of Sums  Combinational &amp;amp; Sequential Circuits: Half Adder, Full Adder, Full Subtractor, Flip-Flops-Rs T Flip-Flops, Shift Registers, Counters </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 2</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/cyber-security/unit-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/cyber-security/unit-2/</guid>
      <description>Security principles The Principles of Security can be classified as follows:-
  Confidentiality :- The Principles specifies that only the sender and receiver will be able to access the informaction shared between them. Confidentiality compromises if an unauthorized person is able to access the message. For Example, let us consider sender A wants to share some confidential information with reveiver B and the information intercepted by the attacker C.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 2</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/data-structures-using-c&#43;&#43;/unit-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/data-structures-using-c&#43;&#43;/unit-2/</guid>
      <description> C++ Programming Concepts: Input And Output In C++ Functions In C++- Value Parameters, Reference Parameters Parameter Passing Function Overloading  Arrays  Pointers  New And Delete Operators  Class And Object  Access Specifiers  Friend Functions  Constructors And Destructor  Operator Overloading  Inheritance And Polymorphism  Exceptions- Throwing An Exception And Handling An Exception </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 2</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/database-management-system-rdbms/unit-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/database-management-system-rdbms/unit-2/</guid>
      <description> Entity relationship (ER) model as a tool of conceptual design: entities &amp;amp; entities set relationship, relationship set &amp;amp; relationship types attributes role participation and mapping constraints keys, strong and weak entities  Advance ER Model Features: generalization specialization aggregation, reducing ER diagram to tables Roles Participation. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 2</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/fundamentals-of-computers-and-pc-software/unit-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/fundamentals-of-computers-and-pc-software/unit-2/</guid>
      <description>Windows: A window is a separate viewing area on a computer display screen in a system that allows multiple viewing areas as part of a graphical user interface ( GUI ). Windows are managed by a windows manager as part of a windowing system . A window can usually be resized by the user.
features of windows — desktop The desktop is the main screen area that you see after you turn on your computer and log on to Windows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 2</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/internet-web-technology/unit-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/internet-web-technology/unit-2/</guid>
      <description> Internet Connectivity: Connectivity types: level one level two level three connectivity Setting up a connection: hardware requirement, selection of a modem software requirement modem configuration Internet accounts by ISP: Telephone line options Protocol options Service options Telephone line options - Dialup connections through the telephone system Dedicated connections through the telephone system ISDN Protocol options - Shell SLIP PPP Service options - E-mail WWW News Firewall etc  Internet Network: Network definition Common terminologies: LAN WAN Node Host Workstation bandwidth Interoperability, Network administrator network security Network Components: Severs Clients Communication Media Types of network: Peer to Peer Clients Server Addressing in Internet: DNS Domain Name and their organization, understanding the Internet Protocol Address Network topologies: Bust Star Ring Ethernet FDDI ATM and Intranet </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 2</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/management-information-system/unit-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/management-information-system/unit-2/</guid>
      <description> Information Systems &amp;amp; Business Strategy: Information Management Who are the users? Manager &amp;amp; Systems Evolution of Computer based information system (CBIS) Model of CBIS Information services organization : Trend to End-User computing justifying the CBIS Achieving the CBIS Managing the CBIS Benefits &amp;amp; Challenges of CBIS implementation Strategic Information System Business level Strategy Firm level Strategy Case Studies </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 2</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/object-oriented-programming-concepts-using-java/unit-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/object-oriented-programming-concepts-using-java/unit-2/</guid>
      <description>Statements  A statement is a single &amp;ldquo;command&amp;rdquo; that is executed by the Java interpreter. By default, the Java interpreter runs one statement after another, in the order they are written. Many of the statements defined by Java, however, are flow-control statements, such as conditionals and loops, that alter this default order of execution in well-defined ways.
   Statement Purpose Syntax     expression side effects var=expr;expr++;method();newType();   compound group statements { statements }   empty do nothing ;   labeled name a statement label : statement   variable declare a variable [final] type name [= value] [, name [= value]] &amp;hellip;;   if conditional if ( expr ) statement [ else statement]   switch conditional switch (expr) { [ case_expr_:_statements_ ] &amp;hellip; [ default:_statements_ ] }   while loop while ( expr ) statement   do loop do statement while ( expr );   for simplified loop for ( init ; test ; increment ) statement   break exit block break [ label ] ;   continue restart loop continue [ label ] ;   return end method return [ expr ] ;   synchronized critical section synchronized ( expr ) { statements }   throw throw exception throw expr ;   try handle exception try {statements} [ catch (type__name) {statements} ] &amp;hellip; [ finally {statements} ]    &amp;ndash; https://docstore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 2</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/operating-system-with-unix-linux/unit-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/operating-system-with-unix-linux/unit-2/</guid>
      <description> Process concept process scheduling operations on processes threads inter-process communication precedence graphs critical section problem semaphores classical problems of synchronization  Deadlock Deadlock problem deadlock characterization deadlock prevention, deadlock avoidance deadlock detection recovery from deadlock Methods for deadlock handling </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 2</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/programming-and-problem-solving-through-c/unit-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/programming-and-problem-solving-through-c/unit-2/</guid>
      <description> Variables and Constants: Character Set Identifiers and Keywords Rules for Forming Identifiers, Data Types Qualifiers Variables Declaring Variables Initialising Variables Constants Types of Constants operators expressions operator precedence and associativity  Conditional Statements and Loops: Decision Control Statements: ifStatement switch Statement, Loop Control Statements: while Loop do-while Statement forLoop Nested Loop gotoStatement, Break Statement Continue Statement  Storage Classes  Managing input/output function: formatted unformatted </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 2</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/software-engineering/unit-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/software-engineering/unit-2/</guid>
      <description> Requirements: Requirements Engineering Establishing the Groundwork Eliciting Requirements Developing use cases Building the requirements model Negotiating validating Requirements Requirements Analysis Requirements Modelling Strategies </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 2</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/web-programming/unit-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/web-programming/unit-2/</guid>
      <description> PHP A Brief History of PHP PHP Characteristics Installing and Configuring PHP on Windows  PHP Language Basics: Lexical Structure Data Types Variables Expressions and Operators Decision Statements Flow Control Statements Embedding PHP in Web Pages  PHP Strings: String Constants Printing Strings Accessing Individual Characters String Handling Functions: length, Word count string position reverse replace </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 2 Algebra of logic</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/discrete-mathematics-and-algebra/unit-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/discrete-mathematics-and-algebra/unit-2/</guid>
      <description> Logic Proposition logic basic logic logical connectives truth tables tautologies contradiction normal forms(conjunctive and disjunctive) modus ponens and modus tollens validity predicate logic universal and existential quantification  Notion of proof: proof by implication converse inverse contrapositive negation, contradiction direct proof proof by using truth table proof by counter example. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 3</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/accounting-and-financial-management/unit-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/accounting-and-financial-management/unit-3/</guid>
      <description>Recording of transactions: Voucher system;  Accounting Process Journals Subsidiary Books Ledger, Cash Book Bank Reconciliation Statement Trial Balance.  Depreciation: Meaning Need &amp;amp; Importance Of Depreciation Methods Of Charging Depreciation. (WDV &amp;amp; SLM). </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 3</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/cloud-computing-concepts/unit-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/cloud-computing-concepts/unit-3/</guid>
      <description> Cloud Management &amp;amp; Virtualization Technology: Resiliency, Provisioning, Asset management, Concepts of Map reduce, Cloud Governance, High Availability and Disaster Recovery  Virtualization: Fundamental Concepts of Compute, storage, networking desktop and Application Virtualization, Virtualization benefits, server Virtualization, Block and file level storage virtualization Hypervisor Management software, Infrastructure Requirements, Virtual LAN(VLAN) and Virtual SAN(VSAN) and their Benefits </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 3</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-graphics-with-multimedia/unit-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-graphics-with-multimedia/unit-3/</guid>
      <description>Coming soon&amp;hellip; Be patient 🙂 Good things takes time. 😉 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 3</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-neworks/unit-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-neworks/unit-3/</guid>
      <description>Limits of Communication RS 449 Interface Standards RS 422 and RS 423  Multiplexing methods : FDM TDM WDM Sampling theorem and quantization Delta Modulation  MAC Sublayer: Multiple access protocols: Pure Aloha Slotted Aloha CSMA Protocols; Collision- Free Protocols IEEE MAC Sublayer protocols: 802.3 802.4 802.5:  Ethernet Fast Ethernet Token Bus Token Ring FDDI, Wireless LANs.  more asdfsadfsad
asdfsadfsadsasdf
sadsf
asdfsadfsadsasdfdf
sadsfs asdfsadfsadsasdfsa draft</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 3</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-oriented-numerical-methods/unit-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-oriented-numerical-methods/unit-3/</guid>
      <description> Difference Operators And Interpolation:  Difference Operators Definition Of Forward, Backward, Shifting, Divided, Difference Central and Averaging Operators and their Relationships.  Interpolation: Newton‘s Forward Interpolation Formula, Newton‘s backward Interpolation Formula Newton‘s divided Interpolation Formula. Lagrange‘s Interpolation Formula. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 3</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-system-architecture/unit-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-system-architecture/unit-3/</guid>
      <description> Cpu Organtsations-  Alu &amp;amp; Control Circuit: Idea About Arithmetic Circuit Program Control, Instruction Sequencing.  Introduction To Microprocessor: Microprocessor Architecture (8086), System Buses, Register, Program Counter, Block Diagram Of A Micro Computer System. Microprocessor Control Signals, Interfacing Devices.  Introcution To Mother Board: Idea About Different Cards And Their Functions, Smps </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 3</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/cyber-security/unit-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/cyber-security/unit-3/</guid>
      <description> Cryptography  Cryptographic mechanisms  Digital signatures  Encryption  Certificates Lattice and reference monitors  Security levels and categories  Lattice diagram  Reference monitors  Security kernel  Hardware security features  Protecting memory </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 3</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/data-structures-using-c&#43;&#43;/unit-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/data-structures-using-c&#43;&#43;/unit-3/</guid>
      <description> Basic Concepts –  Data Structures  Algorithm Specification- Introduction Recursive Algorithms Data Abstraction Performance Analysis- Time Complexity Space Complexity Asymptotic Notation- Big O Omega And Theta Notations Complexity Analysis Examples Introduction To Linear And Non Linear Data  Stack: Definition Array Implementation Of Stack (Static Stack): Operations Push Pop Traverse Applications Of Stack: Infix Prefix Postfix Representation And Evaluation Using Stack, Use Of Stack In Recursive Implementation  Queue: Definition Array Implementation Of Queue (Static Queue): Operations Insert Delete Traverse Introduction To Circular Queue: Definition &amp;amp; Implementation Priority Queue Double Ended Queue Applications Of Queue </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 3</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/database-management-system-rdbms/unit-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/database-management-system-rdbms/unit-3/</guid>
      <description>Fundamentals of set theoretical notations: relations domains attributes tuples  concept of keys: primary key super key alternate key candidate key foreign key  fundamentals of integrity rules: entity integrity referential integrity ,  extension and intention  relational algebra: select project Cartesian product different types of joins: theta joins equi joins natural joins outer joins set operations.  Evaluation of SQL Between clause Distinct Clause Order by Clause Group by Clause SQL Functions Sub queries Handling null value Aggregate function User Defied Function View.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 3</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/fundamentals-of-computers-and-pc-software/unit-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/fundamentals-of-computers-and-pc-software/unit-3/</guid>
      <description> Introduction To Spreadsheet (MS-Excel): Definition And Advantages of Electronic Worksheet Working On Spreadsheets: Cell Referencing Range &amp;amp; Related Operations Setting, Saving And Retrieving Worksheet File Inserting, Deleting, Copying And Moving of Data Cells Inserting And Deleting Rows &amp;amp; Columns Copying, inserting, Renaming the sheet of workbook General Short-cut commands Entering text and numeric data Entering date and time different functions formatting text and numeric data Functions and Other Features: Classification and Usage of Various Built-In-Functions In Worksheet Passwords Protecting A Worksheet Printing of the worksheet page margin setting and adding header and footer Transferring Data to and From Non Worksheet Files Database Handling Creating, Naming &amp;amp; Executing Macros Creating graphs </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 3</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/internet-web-technology/unit-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/internet-web-technology/unit-3/</guid>
      <description> Electronic Mail: Email Networks and Servers Email protocols – SMTP POP3 IMAp4 MIME6 Structure of an Email - Email Address Email Header Body and Attachments  Email Clients: Netscape mail Clients Outlook Express Web based E-mail Email encryption- Address Book Signature File Current Trends on Internet Languages Internet Phone Internet Video collaborative computing e-commerce  Web Publishing and Browsing: Overview SGML Web hosting HTML CGL Documents Interchange Standards Components of Web Publishing, Document management Web Page Design Consideration and Principles Search and Meta Search Engines WWW Browser HTTP Publishing Tools </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 3</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/management-information-system/unit-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/management-information-system/unit-3/</guid>
      <description> Information Systems In the Enterprise: Systems from Management and Functional perspective &amp;amp;their relationship: Executive Information System Decision Support System Sales Marketing Information System Manufacturing Information System Human-Resource Information System Finance &amp;amp; Account Information System Case Studies </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 3</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/object-oriented-programming-concepts-using-java/unit-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/object-oriented-programming-concepts-using-java/unit-3/</guid>
      <description>Definitions and naming conventions for the members of the JAVA classes  A java program may contain many classes of which only one class will have a main method. Class will contain data members and methods that operate on the data members of the class. To write a Java program, we first need to define classes and then put them together. Generally a standard java program consists of following blocks as shown in below figure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 3</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/operating-system-with-unix-linux/unit-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/operating-system-with-unix-linux/unit-3/</guid>
      <description> Concepts of memory management logical and physical address space swapping contiguous and non-contiguous allocation paging segmentation paging combined with segmentation  Concepts of virtual memory demand paging page replacement algorithms allocation of frames thrashing demand segmentation  Security threads protection Intruders Viruses trusted system  Introduction to distributed systems and parallel processing </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 3</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/programming-and-problem-solving-through-c/unit-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/programming-and-problem-solving-through-c/unit-3/</guid>
      <description> Functions: Definition of a Function types of function Declaration of a Function Function Prototypes passing arguments to a function call by value call by reference command line argument recursion  Pointers: pointers and their characteristics address and indirection operators Pointer Type declaration and assignment pointer arithmetic passing pointers to functions array of pointers, introduction to pointer to pointer </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 3</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/software-engineering/unit-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/software-engineering/unit-3/</guid>
      <description> Design Modeling With Uml: Modeling Concepts and Diagrams Use Case Diagrams Class Diagrams Interaction Diagrams State chart Diagrams Activity Diagrams Package Diagrams Component Diagrams Deployment Diagrams Diagram Organization Diagram Extensions  Design Process Design concepts: Abstraction Architecture patterns Separation of Concerns Modularity Information Hiding, Functional Independence Refinement Refactoring Object Oriented Design Concepts, Design Classes Design Model: Data Architectural Interface Component Deployment Level Design Elements </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 3</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/web-programming/unit-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/web-programming/unit-3/</guid>
      <description> Arrays in PHP: Indexed Arrays Associative Arrays Identifying Elements of an Array Storing Data in Arrays, Multidimensional Arrays extracting multiple values converting between arrays and variables Traversing Arrays Sorting  Functions in PHP: Calling a Function Defining a Function Variable Scope Function Parameters Return Values, Variable Functions Anonymous Functions  PHP Object Oriented Programming Concepts: Classes Objects Member Functions Encapsulations Inheritance, Polymorphism </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 3 Algebraic Structure</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/discrete-mathematics-and-algebra/unit-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/discrete-mathematics-and-algebra/unit-3/</guid>
      <description> Binary composition and properties of Binary composition  Definition of algebraic structure; Groyas Semi group Monoid Groups, Abelian Group properties of groups Permutation Groups Sub Group Cyclic Group Rings and Fields (definition and standard results) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 4</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/accounting-and-financial-management/unit-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/accounting-and-financial-management/unit-4/</guid>
      <description> Preparation of final accounts: Preparation of Trading and Profit &amp;amp; Loss Account Balance Sheet of sole proprietary business.  Introduction to Company Final Accounts: Important provisions of Companies Act, 1956 in respect of preparation of Final Accounts. Understanding of final accounts of a Company. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 4</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/cloud-computing-concepts/unit-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/cloud-computing-concepts/unit-4/</guid>
      <description> Cloud Security: Cloud Information Security Fundamentals, Cloud Security Services, Design Principles, Secure Cloud Software Requirements, Policy Implementation,  Security Challenges,  Virtualization security Management,  Cloud Computing Security Architecture </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 4</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-graphics-with-multimedia/unit-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-graphics-with-multimedia/unit-4/</guid>
      <description>Coming soon&amp;hellip; Be patient 🙂 Good things takes time. 😉 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 4</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-neworks/unit-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-neworks/unit-4/</guid>
      <description> Network Layer: Design issues, Routing Algorithms: Optimality Principle, Shortest Path Routing, Flooding, Distance Vector Routing Link State Routing, Hierarchical Routing, B roadcasting Routing, Multicast Routing  The Network Layer in the Internet: Internet Protocol, IP addresses and Internet Control protocols. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 4</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-oriented-numerical-methods/unit-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-oriented-numerical-methods/unit-4/</guid>
      <description> Numerical Differentiation: Numerical Differentiation using Newton‘s Forward Interpolation Formula, Newton‘s Backward Interpolation Formula Newton‘s divided Interpolation Formula  Numerical Integration : General Quadrature Formula, Newton- Cote‘s Formula, Trapezoidal Rule, Simpson‘s One Third Rule, Simpson‘s Three Eight Rule </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 4</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-system-architecture/unit-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-system-architecture/unit-4/</guid>
      <description> Input-Output Organiation: I/O Interface, Properties Of Simple I/O Devices And Their Controller, Isolated Versus Memory-Mapped I/O, Modes Of Data Transfer, Synchronous &amp;amp; Asynchronous Data Transfer, Handshaking, Asynchronous Serial Transfer, I/O Processor </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 4</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/cyber-security/unit-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/cyber-security/unit-4/</guid>
      <description> Security models Chinese wall model Bell-La Padula Biba Non-deducibility Non-interference Other models  Network security  Protocol design principles  ISO architecture  IP security  SSL/TLS  Firewalls,  Intrusion detection </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 4</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/data-structures-using-c&#43;&#43;/unit-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/data-structures-using-c&#43;&#43;/unit-4/</guid>
      <description> Introduction To Linked List: Definition Advantaged Basic Operations On Linked List Stacks And Queues Using Linked List Doubly Linked List Circular Linked List Applications Of Linked List  Searching And Sorting Techniques: Sequential Search Binary Search Insertion Sort Selection Sort Quick Sort Bubble Sort Heap Sort Comparison Of Sorting Methods </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 4</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/database-management-system-rdbms/unit-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/database-management-system-rdbms/unit-4/</guid>
      <description> Functional Dependencies Good &amp;amp; Bad Decomposition Anomalies as a database: A consequences of bad design Universal relation Normalization: 1NF 2NF 3NF &amp;amp; BCNF normal forms multivalued dependency join dependency 4NF 5NF.  Relational Database design  Features of good relational database design  Codd‘s Rule  Integrity constraints  Armstrong Axioms  Closure Set of Functional Dependency  Closure Set of Attributes </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 4</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/fundamentals-of-computers-and-pc-software/unit-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/fundamentals-of-computers-and-pc-software/unit-4/</guid>
      <description> PC Maintenance and Troubleshooting: Opening the PC and identification Study of different blocks Assembling and disassembling  Basic Device Configuration and Installation- Printers Microphone Monitor Mother Board Sound Card Video Card  tips on Trouble Shooting  Introduction to Computer Hardware Components of Mother-boards &amp;amp; its types Ports Slots Connectors add on cards Power supply units cabinet types  Storage devices: Primary storage medium Secondary storage medium  Introduction to servers and network security Types of servers: Files servers Email Servers Proxy servers etc  Basics of Internet and Intranet: Types of Internet connections: Dialup Broadband Leased Line Wi-Fi Wi-Max 2G 3G 4G WWW, E-mails Search Engines Social Networking Cloud application Audio-video Conferencing Voice over Internet Protocol (VOIP) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 4</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/internet-web-technology/unit-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/internet-web-technology/unit-4/</guid>
      <description> HTML Programming Basics: HTML page structure HTML Attributes HEAD Elements Input elements , HTML Text HTML links HTML document tables HTML Frames HTML Images HTML multimedia  Introduction to CSS  Java Script: Introduction Basic Syntax Control Structures Writing Functions Working with Arrays The Document Object Model Events Handling Using Browser Objects Object Oriented in JavaScript </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 4</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/management-information-system/unit-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/management-information-system/unit-4/</guid>
      <description> Information Technology for Competitive Advantage: Information resources Firm in its environment What are the information resources? Who manages the information resources? Strategic planning for information resources End-User Computing as a strategic issue, Information resource management concept Case Studies </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 4</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/object-oriented-programming-concepts-using-java/unit-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/object-oriented-programming-concepts-using-java/unit-4/</guid>
      <description> Inheritance  Super class  Sub class  Method overloading  interface  thread  Multithreading example  synchronized  Exception (try-catch-final blocks examples)  examples and exercises </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 4</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/operating-system-with-unix-linux/unit-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/operating-system-with-unix-linux/unit-4/</guid>
      <description> Unix operating system background philosophy help facility The file system structure of file system Basic Command related to file system  Unix Utilities: more file wc file comparison ( cmp, comm &amp;amp; diff) cmp comm diff lp banner cal date who tty, sty commands  The Bourne shell: sh preceding a command by its own combining commands, pattern matching echo pipes tees shell variables shell scripts simple filters Advanced filters  The process: shell process parent and children process status system processes multiple jobs foreground and background wait commands pre mature termination of process job execution with low priority multiple jobs in foreground shell layers timing processes </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 4</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/programming-and-problem-solving-through-c/unit-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/programming-and-problem-solving-through-c/unit-4/</guid>
      <description> Array: one dimensional array Declaration and Initialization Insertion of an element Deletion of an element form an array finding the largest/smallest element in an array Two dimensional arrays addition of matrices multiplication of matrices  String: Declaration and Initialization of Strings Array of Strings Built-in String Functions strlen strcpy strcmp, strcat strlwr strrev Other String Functions  Structures and Unions: Declaration of Structures Accessing the Members of a Structure Initializing Structures, Structures as Function Arguments Structures and Arrays Unions Initializing an Union Accessing the Members of an Union </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 4</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/software-engineering/unit-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/software-engineering/unit-4/</guid>
      <description> Software Implementation: Structured coding Techniques Coding Styles Standards and Guidelines Documentation Guidelines  Modern Programming Language Features: Type checking User defined data types Data Abstraction Exception Handling Concurrency Mechanism </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 4</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/web-programming/unit-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/web-programming/unit-4/</guid>
      <description> Form Handling in PHP: Setting Up Web Pages to Communicate with PHP Handling Text Fields Text Areas Check Boxes Radio Buttons List Boxes Password Controls Hidden Controls Image Maps  File Handling in PHP: Working with files and directories File Open and Read File Create and Write Reading and writing Character in file Reading entire file Rename and Delete File getting information of files ownership and permissions </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 4 Graphs</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/discrete-mathematics-and-algebra/unit-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/discrete-mathematics-and-algebra/unit-4/</guid>
      <description> Graph terminology types of graph connected graphs components of graph Euler graph Hamiltonian path and circuits Graph coloring Chromatic number  Tree: Definition types of tree rooted tree binary tree Properties of trees binary search tree tree traversing preorder inorder postorder  Finite Automata: Basic concepts of Automation theory Deterministic finite </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 5</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/accounting-and-financial-management/unit-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/accounting-and-financial-management/unit-5/</guid>
      <description> Computerised Accounting: Computers and Financial application Accounting Software packages  Overview of computerized accounting system - Salient features and significance, Concept of grouping of accounts, Codification of accounts, Maintaining the hierarchy of ledger, Generating Accounting Reports </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 5</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/cloud-computing-concepts/unit-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/cloud-computing-concepts/unit-5/</guid>
      <description> Market Based Management of Clouds  Federated Clouds/Inter Cloud: Characterization &amp;amp; Definition, Cloud Federation Stack, Third party Cloud Services  Case Study: Google App Engine, Microsoft Azure, Hadoop, Amazon, Aneka </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 5</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-graphics-with-multimedia/unit-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-graphics-with-multimedia/unit-5/</guid>
      <description>Coming soon&amp;hellip; Be patient 🙂 Good things takes time. 😉 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 5</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-neworks/unit-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-neworks/unit-5/</guid>
      <description> Transport Layer: Elements of Transport Protocols, Addressing, Connection Establishment &amp;amp; Release, Flow Control &amp;amp; Buffering, Multiplexing  Introduction to UDP &amp;amp; TCP.  Application layer: DNS, WWW and HTTP, Cookies, Proxy Server E-mail Protocols (SMTP, POP3, IMAP, MIME), FTP, TELNET  Network Security: Cryptography, Symmetric- key Algorithms: DES, AES, Public-key Algorithms: RSA, Digital Signatures. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 5</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-oriented-numerical-methods/unit-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-oriented-numerical-methods/unit-5/</guid>
      <description> Numerical Solutions of Ordinary Differential Equations: Euler‘s Method , Euler‘s Modifies Method. Tailor‘s Series Method, Picard‘s Method, RungaKutta Second Order and Fourth order Method. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 5</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-system-architecture/unit-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-system-architecture/unit-5/</guid>
      <description> MEMORY ORGANISATION : Auxiliary memory Magnetic drum Disk &amp;amp; Tape Semi conductor memories  Memory Hierarchy  Associative memory  Virtual memory  Address space &amp;amp; memory space  Address Mapping  Page table  Page replacement  Cache memory  Hit Ratio  Mapping techniques  Writing into cache </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 5</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/cyber-security/unit-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/cyber-security/unit-5/</guid>
      <description> Unix security and Windows security  Subjects objects and access control software security and database security  Memory management  Data and code  Relational databases Access control in databases  Statistical database security  General security principles  Access components  Access decisions  Administration and management issues </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 5</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/data-structures-using-c&#43;&#43;/unit-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/data-structures-using-c&#43;&#43;/unit-5/</guid>
      <description> Tree: Trees-Basic Terminology , Binary Trees Tree Representations As Array And Linked List Basic Operations On Binary Tree Traversal Of Binary Trees:- Inorder Preorder Postorder Applications Of Binary Tree Threaded Binary Tree AVL Tree Introduction To B-Tree &amp;amp; B+ Tree Hash Table Collision Resolution Technique  Graphs: Definition Terminology Directed Undirected Graph Weighted Graph Representation Of Graph, Graph Traversal- Depth First Search Breadth First Search Spanning Tree Minimum Spanning Tree Shortest Path Algorithm </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 5</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/database-management-system-rdbms/unit-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/database-management-system-rdbms/unit-5/</guid>
      <description> Basic concepts: - Indexing and Hashing B-tree Index files Hashing: Static hash function Dynamic hash function,  Index definition in SQL: Multiple key accesses.  Transaction Management  ACID properties,  Serializability  Concurrency Control  Lock types of Locks Two Phase Locking Protocol Check Points Recovery Techniques Deferred and Immediate data modification.  Emerging Database Technology: Data Warehouse Data Mining Distributed database Mobile Database Object Oriented Database Geographical Database </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 5</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/fundamentals-of-computers-and-pc-software/unit-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/fundamentals-of-computers-and-pc-software/unit-5/</guid>
      <description> Overview of System Analysis and Design Business System Concepts System Development Life Cycle Preliminary Investigation Feasibility Study System Analysis System Design and Testing Implementation &amp;amp; Evaluation  Overview of MIS: Introduction Role of IT MIS - characteristics and application areas Business and Technology trends - specialization, management by methodology decentralization internationalization etc  Characteristics of a good Business Unit Data and Information Difference between data and information Introduction to data Processing Fields Records Files Types of files: Master files Transaction file  Introduction to ERP  Introduction to SCM </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 5</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/internet-web-technology/unit-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/internet-web-technology/unit-5/</guid>
      <description> Introduction to AJAX : AJAX RIA &amp;amp; WEB 2.0 The XML HTTP Request Object  Using AJAX in Web Applications  Interactivity Tools: ASP VB Script JAVA Script JAVA and Front Page Flash  Internet Security Management Concepts Information Privacy and Copyright Issues, Overview of Internet Security Firewalls Internet Security Management Concepts and Information Privacy and Copyright Issues Basics of asymmetric cryptosystems </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 5</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/management-information-system/unit-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/management-information-system/unit-5/</guid>
      <description> E-Commerce &amp;amp; International Information System : E-Commerce Introduction to E-Commerce Business Intelligence E-Commerce strategy Electronic Data Interchange E-commerce methodology E-commerce technology Business application of the Internet Electronic Business success strategies International Information System Managing International Information Systems: IIS architecture Global business drivers challenges Strategy: divide &amp;amp; conquer appease cooptation business organization Problems in Implementing global information systems Computer crime ethics &amp;amp; social issues </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 5</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/object-oriented-programming-concepts-using-java/unit-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/object-oriented-programming-concepts-using-java/unit-5/</guid>
      <description> Java Virtual machine concept  Java Platform overview  programming Examples to clarify use of object  threads  exceptions and packages for I/O  file and string handling  examples and exercises </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 5</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/operating-system-with-unix-linux/unit-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/operating-system-with-unix-linux/unit-5/</guid>
      <description> Communication and scheduling Execute at later running jobs periodically  Programming with shell: system variable profile conditional execution script termination Conditional and loop control statements set and shift statement  System Administration: super user security user services floppy disk management operation files system administration backups </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 5</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/programming-and-problem-solving-through-c/unit-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/programming-and-problem-solving-through-c/unit-5/</guid>
      <description> File Handling: Concept of files Open a file using the function fopen() Close a file using the function fclose( ) file opening mode Input and Output using file pointers Character Input and Output in Files, String Input / Output Functions Formatted Input / Output Functions Block Input / Output Functions, Sequential Vs Random Access Files text file vs binary file  Graphics programming: introduction, functions stylish liens drawing and filling images palettes and colours </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 5</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/software-engineering/unit-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/software-engineering/unit-5/</guid>
      <description> Testing And Maintenance: Testing Software Quality Software Quality Dilemma Achieving Software Quality Testing: Strategic Approach to software Testing Strategic Issues Testing: Strategies for Conventional Software Object oriented software Web Apps Validating Testing System Testing Art of Debugging  Maintenance: Software Maintenance Software Supportability Reengineering Business Process Reengineering Software Reengineering Reverse Engineering Restructuring Forward Engineering Economics of Reengineering </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 5</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/web-programming/unit-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/web-programming/unit-5/</guid>
      <description> Database Access: Using PHP to access a database  Introduction to MySql connectivity with MySql  XML: What is XML? XML document structure PHP and XML XML parser the document object model the simple XML extension changing a value with simple XML </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit - 5 Determinant and Matrices</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/discrete-mathematics-and-algebra/unit-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/discrete-mathematics-and-algebra/unit-5/</guid>
      <description> Determinant Determinants properties solution of simultaneous equations by Cramer‘s rule  Matrices Definition of special kinds of matrices Review of matrices inverse of matrix Normal forms Linear dependence Rank Application to theory of solutions of system of linear equations linear transformation Orthogonal matrices Unitary matrices Hermitian matrices Eigen values and Eigen vectors </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazing Tools</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/amazing-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/amazing-tools/</guid>
      <description>Coming soon&amp;hellip; Be patient 🙂 Good things takes time. 😉 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/books/</guid>
      <description>Coming soon&amp;hellip; Be patient 🙂 Good things takes time. 😉 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Year Syllabus</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/bca-syllabus/first-year-syllabus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/bca-syllabus/first-year-syllabus/</guid>
      <description>Download or Print First Year BCA Syllabus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/accounting-and-financial-management/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/accounting-and-financial-management/resources/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/cloud-computing-concepts/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/cloud-computing-concepts/resources/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-graphics-with-multimedia/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-graphics-with-multimedia/resources/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-neworks/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-neworks/resources/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-oriented-numerical-methods/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-oriented-numerical-methods/resources/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-system-architecture/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/computer-system-architecture/resources/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/cyber-security/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/cyber-security/resources/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/data-structures-using-c&#43;&#43;/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/data-structures-using-c&#43;&#43;/resources/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/database-management-system-rdbms/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/database-management-system-rdbms/resources/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/discrete-mathematics-and-algebra/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/discrete-mathematics-and-algebra/resources/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/fundamentals-of-computers-and-pc-software/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/fundamentals-of-computers-and-pc-software/resources/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/internet-web-technology/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/internet-web-technology/resources/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/management-information-system/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/management-information-system/resources/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/object-oriented-programming-concepts-using-java/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/object-oriented-programming-concepts-using-java/resources/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/operating-system-with-unix-linux/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/operating-system-with-unix-linux/resources/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/programming-and-problem-solving-through-c/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/programming-and-problem-solving-through-c/resources/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/software-engineering/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/software-engineering/resources/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/web-programming/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/web-programming/resources/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second Year Syllabus</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/bca-syllabus/second-year-syllabus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/bca-syllabus/second-year-syllabus/</guid>
      <description>Download or Print Second Year BCA Syllabus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Third Year Syllabus</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/bca-syllabus/third-year-syllabus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/bca-syllabus/third-year-syllabus/</guid>
      <description>Download or Print Third Year BCA Syllabus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Useful Websites</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/useful-websites/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/useful-websites/</guid>
      <description>Coming soon&amp;hellip; Be patient 🙂 Good things takes time. 😉 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Useful Youtube Channels</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/useful-youtube-channels/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 16:11:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/useful-youtube-channels/</guid>
      <description>Coming soon&amp;hellip; Be patient 🙂 Good things takes time. 😉 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archive</title>
      <link>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/archives/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xvishaldongre.github.io/bleeding-edge-bcanotes/archives/</guid>
      <description>archives</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
